http://www.lesmills.com/privacy-policy/

Loading...
0 Location(s) found near you
Find a class Nothing close by? Try for free* at home with LES MILLS On Demand.*Cancel anytime during free trial.
Return to Map
No Results We can't see any results for that search. Hint: try using the name of the nearest city. OK
Les Mills Home
Rest of the World
Global Asia-Pacific China India Israel Japan Middle East Russia
Americas
Argentina Bolivia Brazil Chile Colombia Ecuador Mexico Panama Paraguay Peru Uruguay United States
Europe
Balkan Belgium Denmark Estonia Finland France Germany Greece Italy Netherlands Norway Poland Spain Sweden United Kingdom
FITNESS CLASSES
BODYPUMP BODYCOMBAT BODYBALANCE CXWORX BODYATTACK RPM SH'BAM BODYJAM BODYSTEP LES MILLS TONE THE TRIP LES MILLS BARRE
HIGH INTENSITY INTERVAL TRAINING
LES MILLS SPRINT LES MILLS GRIT STRENGTH LES MILLS GRIT ATHLETIC LES MILLS GRIT CARDIO
YOUTH Classes
BORN TO MOVE 2-3 YEARS BORN TO MOVE 4-5 YEARS BORN TO MOVE 6-7 YEARS BORN TO MOVE 8-12 YEARS BORN TO MOVE 13-16 YEARS
AT HOME
START YOUR FREE TRIAL
START YOUR FREE TRIAL
Member login Workouts Workout plans Technique Equipment FAQs
Workout categories
Strength training Cardio workouts Indoor cycling workouts HIIT workouts Ab workouts Dance workouts Flexibility workouts Guided meditation Kids workouts
Instructors
GET PAID TO DO WHAT YOU LOVE Train as an Instructor
JOIN THE TEAM about training FIND TRAINING
onGOING DEVELOPMENT iNSTRUCTOR nEWS Get in touch
CLUBS & FACILITIES
WORLD UNITED
Join the biggest fitness event of the year
Partner With us Get In touch
Our Programs Virtual CLASSES
Research & Insights Tools & Resources
Fit Planet
Want more health and fitness inspiration? Sign up to Fit Planet
Fitness Health NUTRITION
Pregnancy & Child Green Living Media
Shop
All Merchandise Clothing
Equipment Les Mills & Polar
Events
Workouts
FITNESS CLASSES
BODYPUMP BODYCOMBAT BODYBALANCE CXWORX BODYATTACK RPM SH'BAM BODYJAM BODYSTEP LES MILLS TONE THE TRIP LES MILLS BARRE
HIGH INTENSITY INTERVAL TRAINING
LES MILLS SPRINT LES MILLS GRIT STRENGTH LES MILLS GRIT ATHLETIC LES MILLS GRIT CARDIO
YOUTH Classes
BORN TO MOVE 2-3 YEARS BORN TO MOVE 4-5 YEARS BORN TO MOVE 6-7 YEARS BORN TO MOVE 8-12 YEARS BORN TO MOVE 13-16 YEARS
AT HOME
START YOUR FREE TRIAL About Work out now LOGIN
Instructors
Training Ongoing development News get in touch Book training
CLUBS & FACILITIES
our Programs Virtual Research & Insights TOOLS & RESOURCES Get in touch
Fit Planet
Fitness Health Nutrition Pregnancy & Child Green Living Media Our Tribe Subscribe
Shop
Clothing Equipment Les Mills & Polar
Events
Privacy Policy
Direct Marketing
Content License
Cookie Declaration
On Demand
LES MILLS PRIVACY POLICY
Last updated 04 May 2018 Les Mills Privacy Policy in Swedish.Les Mills sekretesspolicy på svenska. Introduction Les Mills is committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. This policy (together with our website terms of use (www.lesmills.com/website-terms) and any other policy developed on this website from time to time and notified on any part of the site) sets out the basis on which any personal information we collect from you, or that you provide to us, will be processed by us.
Please read the following carefully to understand our practices regarding your personal information and how we will treat it. This policy may change from time to time and, if it does, the latest version will be available on our website or our app (and, where appropriate, brought to your attention). This privacy policy was last updated on 4 May 2018. Key Points
Les Mills International Limited is the data controller of personal information processed through your use of our website or app. The type of the personal information processed by us includes information that you provide when using our site or services, technical information about your device, settings and website use, information that we receive from third parties, such as other website providers, ad networks, social media companies and health and fitness clubs and, where applicable, information relating to your role as instructor. We use your data, amongst other things, to provide you with our site and services or information about our site and services, tailor our services to you, carry out analysis of our services, provide (or allow others to provide) targeted ads, comply with any legal or regulatory obligation and (if you are an instructor) assess your performance and provide information relating to your role. We may send you marketing materials relating to our services which you can opt out of at any time. We share data with our service providers and other third parties for the performance of our contractual obligations to you, to provide you with information, for the serving of advertising and (where relevant) run credit and background checks. You have a number of rights that you may exercise in relation to our use of your personal data, and you may exercise these by contacting us through the communication methods set out in the 'Your rights' section below.
You can find information about us and how we collect, use and store your personal data in each section of this policy:
Who are we Information we collect from you How your information will be used Disclosure of your information Les Mills instructors Where we store your personal information Data retention Security of your information Social networks Linked Sites Public forums Children Your rights Changes to our privacy policy Contact Cookie notice Differences between notices
WHO ARE WE This website or our app (the “site”) is controlled by Les Mills International Limited (“we”, “us”, “our”) whose registered office is at 22 Centre Street, Auckland 1010, New Zealand. While our instructor and club portals are ultimately controlled by us, the day to day operation of these portals is carried out by the following Les Mills companies in your territory. Les Mills UK Fitness Limited operates the UK instructor and club portals, Les Mills United States Trading Inc., operates the US instructor and club portals and Les Mills Nordic AB operates the Nordic instructor and club portals. We, along with the relevant Les Mills Company in your territory (if you are using our instructor or club portals), are joint data controllers i.e., responsible for the processing of your personal information. In this Privacy Policy, the “Les Mills Companies” means all subsidiaries and affiliate companies from time to time owned by us. If you require a full list of entities comprising the Les Mills Companies, please contact us as described in the “Contact” section below. “Instructor" means any person authorised to instruct Les Mills programs or who has entered into an instructor agreement (“Instructor Agreement”) with us, the Les Mills Companies or an authorised distributor. Back to top
INFORMATION WE COLLECT FROM YOU We will collect and process the following information about you: Information you give us This is information about you that you give us when you browse or use the site, correspond with us by phone, SMS, email, social media or otherwise. It includes information you provide when:
You register to use our site; Subscribe to our service; Search for a product; Place an order on our site; Participate in discussion boards or other social media functions on our site; Enter a competition; When you report a problem with our site;
The information you give us includes your name, address, date of birth, e-mail address and phone number, financial and credit card information, personal description and photographs, videos, images or comments. If you are an Instructor, we will collect additional information about you in relation to your role including details of the classes and clubs you are affiliated with, purchasing history, payment information, event/training attendance, certification information and hours worked. Information we collect about you With regard to each of your visits to our site we will automatically collect the following information:
Technical information, including the IP address used to connect your computer or device to the Internet, your login information, browser type and version, time zone setting, anonymised location data, browser plug-in types and versions, operating system and platform; Information about your visit, including the full URL, clickstream to, through and from our site (including date and time), pages or products you viewed or searched for, page response times, download errors, length of visits to certain pages, page interaction information (such as scrolling, clicks, and mouse-overs), methods used to browse away from the page.
Information we receive from other sources Other Les Mills websites: We will receive information about you if you use any of the other websites operated by Les Mills Companies or the other services the Les Mills Companies provide. Third parties: We also work closely with third parties (including, for example, business partners, authorised distributors, health and/or fitness clubs or any other organization that Les Mills has licensed to conduct Les Mills programs (“Licensed Clubs”), sub-contractors in technical, payment and delivery services, advertising networks, analytics providers, advertisers, search information providers, credit reference agencies, third parties that enable sign-on functionality and social network integration) and will receive information about you from them. Social Media: If you connect with us via certain social media platforms, or you choose to use features on this site or the websites of other Les Mills Companies that connect to your online profiles or social media accounts (“Social Media Accounts”), we will collect any information that you permit through your settings on those Social Media Accounts. For example, if you log in to our site using your Facebook account and you have allowed Facebook to share your profile information with us, we may collect that information. Information we receive from your Social Media Accounts will include the email address, first and last name, location (hometown and country), gender, date of birth, likes, interests, number of connections, occupation, posts or other social activity. The information that your social media platform may provide to us via your Social Media Account may change from time to time. Please review your Social Media Account privacy settings to control what information is shared with us. Back to top
HOW YOUR INFORMATION WILL BE USED We use information held about you in the following ways. Whenever possible, we anonymise the data so that it cannot be connected to any individual person. Information you give to us (including through Social Media Accounts) A. We process data for the following purposes based on our legitimate interests:
to provide you with information about other goods and services we offer that are similar to those that you have already purchased or enquired about; to ensure that content from our site is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer; to tailor your experience on the site; for data analysis, testing, research, statistical, editorial, feedback and survey purposes; to comply with legal and regulatory requirements.
B. We will process data for the following purposes based on our performance of a contract:
to carry out our obligations arising from any contracts entered into between you and us; respond to your queries; to provide you with the information, products and services that you request from us; to notify you about changes to our service; to allow you to share information on our site on third party social media platforms.
C. We will process data for the following purposes based on your consent:
to provide you with the latest information and offers relating to health and fitness, or allow authorised third parties to provide information to you about goods and services; to sign you up to Reebok One in order to be able to receive a 25% discount if you are a Les Mills instructor.
Information we collect about you A. We will process data for the following purposes based on our legitimate interests:
to administer our site and for internal operations, including troubleshooting, data analysis, testing, research, statistical and survey purposes; to improve our site to ensure that content is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer; as part of our efforts to keep our site safe and secure; to measure or understand the effectiveness of advertising we serve to you and others, and to deliver relevant advertising to you; to make suggestions and recommendations to you and other users of our site about goods or services that may interest you or them; to provide (or permit third parties to provide) targeted advertising via websites you visit about goods or services that you may find interesting (see more on this in our Cookies Notice below); To track the progress and number of entries in competitions and promotions.
B. We will process data for the following purposes based on your consent:
to allow you to participate in interactive features of our service when you choose to do so.
Information we receive from other sources. We will combine information we receive from other sources with the information you give to us and information we collect about you. We will use this information and the combined information for the purposes set out above (depending on the types of information we receive). Back to top
DISCLOSURE OF YOUR INFORMATION Service Providers For some of the purposes for which we use personal data (see above), we will engage a third party. If such third party needs access to personal data to carry out its task, we will share the data with them, we will ensure that the third party will only use the data based on our instructions. Such a party is a processor on our behalf and we remain responsible for your data. We will engage the following processors:
Companies that provide services to us (including Les Mills Companies), such as vendors, service providers, and other partners who globally support our business. These third parties provide services such as providing technical infrastructure services, analyzing how our services are used, measuring the effectiveness of ads and services, providing customer service, facilitating payments, or conducting academic research and surveys. These partners must adhere to strict confidentiality obligations in a way that is consistent with this policy and the agreements we enter into with them; and Analytics and search engine providers that assist us in the improvement and optimisation of our site. We want our site and advertising to be as relevant and interesting to you as it can be. With this in mind, we use all of the information we have about you to show you relevant ads, and in order to be able to optimize our site. We do not share information that personally identifies you (personally identifiable information is information like name or email address that can by itself be used to contact you or identifies who you are) with advertising, measurement or analytics partners unless you give us permission. We may provide these partners with information about the reach and effectiveness of their advertising without providing information that personally identifies you, or if we have aggregated the information so that it does not personally identify you.
Other Third Parties We will, based either on your explicit consent, or otherwise when we have the right to do so according to applicable personal data regulations, share your personal information with:
Les Mills Companies; the following selected third parties:
business partners, authorised distributors, suppliers, service providers, Les Mills licensed clubs and sub-contractors for the performance of any contract we enter into with you; business partners, authorised distributors, suppliers, service providers, Les Mills licensed clubs and sub-contractors to provide you with information about promotions and offers, or for any of the other purposes described the “How your information will be used” section above; advertisers and advertising networks that require the data to select and serve relevant advertising to you and others. Except as stated in the bullet point directly below, we do not disclose information about identifiable individuals to our advertisers, but we will provide them with aggregate information about our users (for example, we may inform them that 500 men aged under 30 have clicked on their ad on any given day). We will also use such aggregate information to help advertisers reach the kind of audience they want to target (for example, women within a certain postcode). We will make use of the personal information we have collected from you to enable us to comply with our advertisers' wishes by displaying their advertising to that target audience; social media or other similar platforms so that we can serve relevant content to you via that platform. For example, we may share your email address with Facebook so that we can include you within a custom audience that we (or a third party on our behalf) will serve content to on Facebook, or we may create an audience of other Facebook users based on the information in your Facebook profile; credit reference agencies for the purpose of assessing your credit score where this is a condition of us entering into a contract with you.
Disclosure under certain circumstances We will, based either on your explicit consent, or otherwise when we have the right to do so according to applicable personal data regulations also disclose your personal information to third parties in the following circumstances:
In the event that we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we will disclose your personal information to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets; If the Les Mills Company that controls this site or substantially all of its assets are acquired by a third party, in which case personal information held by it about its customers will be one of the transferred assets; If we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal information in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our website terms of use (www.lesmills.com/website-terms) and other agreements; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of any Les Mills Company, our customers, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction; Where you have otherwise consented that we may do so.
Back to top
LES MILLS INSTRUCTORS Additional purposes for which Instructor’s personal information will be used
We (or Licensed Clubs) may give Instructors the option to share their personal information with Licensed Clubs via our club portal at https://sso.lesmills.com/login (“Club Portal”). Where Instructors agree to share their personal information via the Club Portal, Licensed Clubs will be able to access, process and use that personal information to: (i) facilitate and maintain the relationship between the Licensed Club and Instructor; (ii) purchase Les Mills releases on behalf of nominated Instructors; (iii) purchase event tickets on behalf of nominated Instructors; (iv) contact, or respond to contact requests by, Instructors who are seeking Licensed Clubs to be affiliated with; and (v) for other purposes as legally required or lawfully permitted from time to time. If you are a Licensed Club and you provide us with Personal Information about Instructors (“Instructor Information”), you hereby warrant that you have all necessary consents under applicable law to provide that Instructor Information to us and that we may use that Instructor Information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. You agree to indemnify, defend and hold us harmless from and against any claims, costs, losses, liabilities and damage arising out of our use of that Instructor Information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. If you are an Instructor, we will also use information that you provide us, we collect about you or we receive from other sources for the following purposes (on the basis of our performance of a contract with you or, where this does not apply, on the basis of our legitimate interests):
the review, management and administration of all aspects of your role (including performance, assessment and payment) as an instructor (including providing you with access to the Les Mills instructor portal at http://w2.lesmills.com/home/login (“Instructor Portal”) and information about training, assessment, certification, events and the supply of Les Mills releases); providing information about your certification, continuing education, assessment and training to your Licensed Club(s); ensuring that the Licensed Club(s) you are affiliated with are complying with their obligations to us; ensuring that you are complying with the terms of your Instructor Agreement and the Instructor Portal and for any legal proceedings arising in relation to it; the management and monitoring of the performance of group fitness (including Instructor performance) at Licensed Clubs and analysing trends in group fitness performance in the fitness industry.
Additional disclosure of Instructor's personal information
If you are an Instructor, we will, based either on your explicit consent, or otherwise when we have the right to do so according to applicable personal data regulations, publish your name in newsletters and on our websites in relation to your role as an Instructor.
Back to top
WHERE WE STORE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION AND INTERNATIONAL TRANSFERS Individuals (especially within the European Economic Area, or “EEA”) should be aware that we and other third party recipients of their personal information, such as the Les Mills Companies or our service providers will not be located within your jurisdiction or within the EEA. For instance, personal data may be transferred to New Zealand in connection with the purposes stated above. Steps will be taken to protect your personal information in that instance consistent with applicable law, for example entering into contractual clauses which mirror the EC-model clauses where personal data concerning EU citizens is shared with a party outside the EEA based in a country which is deemed not to have adequate data protection safeguards in place. All information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers or on the secure servers or secure services controlled by third parties on our behalf. Any payment transactions will be encrypted using SSL technology. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password which enables you to access certain parts of our site, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share a password with anyone. Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our site; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access. Back to top
DATA RETENTION We retain the personal information we collect only if we need it to support justifiable business requirements or when our lawful purposes for using the information requires retention. When we no longer require personal information we or our third party suppliers will securely delete and/or archive the information. For more information on where and how long your personal information is stored, and for more information on your rights of erasure and portability, please contact us at info@lesmills.com. Back to top
SECURITY OF YOUR INFORMATION To help protect the privacy of data and personally identifiable information you transmit through use of our site and portals, we maintain physical, technical and administrative safeguards. We update and test our security technology on an ongoing basis. We restrict access to your personal data to those employees who need to know that information to provide benefits or services to you. In addition, we train our employees about the importance of confidentiality and maintaining the privacy and security of your information. We commit to taking appropriate disciplinary measures to enforce our employees' privacy responsibilities. Back to top
SOCIAL NETWORKS You may be able to log in to our site using social sign-in services such as Facebook Connect. These services will authenticate your identity and provide you the option to share certain personal information with us such as your name and email address to pre-populate our sign up form. Services like Facebook Connect give you the option to post information about your activities on this site to your profile page to share with others within your network. Back to top
LINKED SITES This site, our newsletters and other communications will from time to time contain links and/or banners that take you to other websites. We are not responsible for the reliability of the content or privacy practices of such other websites. Our site may also contain social media features, such as the Facebook Like button. These features will collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and will set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Social media features and widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our site. Your interactions with these features are also governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it. Back to top
PUBLIC FORUMS We may provide you with chat features, instant messaging, message boards, community forums and/or news groups through the site or otherwise. Please remember that any information that you disclose in public areas of the site will become public information, and be accessible to the public. We do not intend (but reserve the right) to monitor, moderate or screen the contents of user postings. We bear no responsibility for any such content and you should be cautious when considering whether to disclose your personal information in the on the site through public or private forums. Back to top
CHILDREN We do not knowingly collect information from children under the age of 16 and the site and any associated apps are not targeted to children under the age of 16. We encourage parents and guardians to take an active role in their children’s online activities and interests. Back to top
YOUR RIGHTS Access to Your Personal Information You have the right to request access to certain personal data that we hold about you including any information we have shared to our Les Mills Companies or third parties and/or processors, subject to certain conditions and limited exceptions set out in relevant data privacy laws. If you wish to do so, please email your request to info@lesmills.com. We will be as open as we can with you but sometimes we might not hold any personal information about you or may have to withhold personal information from you. For example, where the information is not personal information about you, is commercially sensitive, is legally privileged, relates to the personal information of another person, or it may impact on the safety or security of our employees or customers to release it. In these circumstances, we will withhold the information but we'll tell you why. You must provide us with accurate information. If any of your details change, please inform us and we will update your personal information in line with our obligations under the relevant laws. You have the right to ask us not to use your personal information for marketing purposes. We will usually inform you (before collecting your data) if we intend to use your data for such purposes or if we intend to disclose your information to any third party for such purposes. You can exercise the right at any time by contacting us at info@lesmills.com or by using any other opt-out method that we provide in the communication, such as an 'unsubscribe' link in emails. You may also have special rights under data protection legislation in the European Union, in addition to those rights set out above. If this legislation applies to you, you may also request information about: the purpose of the processing; the categories of personal data concerned; who else outside the Les Mills Companies might have received the data from us; what the source of the information was (if you didn’t provide it directly to us); and how long it will be stored. You have a right to:
request that we correct (rectify) the record of your personal data maintained by us if it is inaccurate or out of date; request that we erase that data or cease processing it, subject to certain exceptions; ask us not to process your personal information for the legitimate interests that we have set out above. In certain circumstances we may not be able to stop using your personal information but, if that is the case, we'll let you know and tell you why; receive the personal information that you have provided to us in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format, and to transmit that data to another data controller; and lodge a complaint with the appropriate data protection authority if you have concerns about how we processes your personal data.
If you wish to exercise any of the above rights, please your request to info@lesmills.com. Back to top
CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY Any changes we make to our privacy policy in the future will be posted on this page and, where appropriate, notified to you by e-mail. Please check back frequently to see any updates or changes to our privacy policy. Back to top
CONTACT Questions, comments and requests regarding this privacy policy are welcomed and should be addressed to info@lesmills.com. Our address is 22 Centre Street, Auckland, New Zealand 1010. Back to top
COOKIE NOTICE The site uses cookies to distinguish you from other users. This helps us to provide you with a good experience when you browse the site and also allows us to improve the site. A cookie is a small file of letters and numbers that we store on your browser or the hard drive of your computer. Cookies contain information that is transferred to your computer's hard drive. We use the following cookies:
Strictly necessary cookies. These are cookies that are required for the operation of the site. They include, for example, cookies that enable you to log into secure areas of the site. Analytical/performance cookies. They allow us to recognise and count the number of visitors and to see how visitors move around the site when they are using it. This helps us to improve the way the site works, for example, by ensuring that users are finding what they are looking for easily. Functionality cookies. These are used to recognise you when you return to the site. This enables us to personalise our content for you, greet you by name and remember your preferences (for example, your choice of language or region). Targeting cookies. These cookies record your visit to the site, the pages you have visited and the links you have followed. We will use this information to make the site and the advertising displayed on it more relevant to your interests. We may also share this information with third parties for this purpose.
Some pages of the site and our e-mails will contain small electronic files known as web beacons (also referred to as clear gifs, pixel tags, and single-pixel gifs) that typically work in conjunction with cookies to identify our users and user behaviour over time, for example, to count users who have visited certain web pages or opened an email and for other related website statistics (for example, recording the popularity of certain website content and verifying system and server integrity). Please note that third parties (including, for example, advertising networks and providers of external services like web traffic analysis services) will also use cookies on our site, over which we have no control. These cookies are likely to be analytical/performance cookies or targeting cookies. Advertising networks in particular collect information about your online activities over time and across different websites and use this information to provide you with interest-based (behavioural) advertising or other targeted content. If you'd like to opt out of interest based advertising, please go to the Network Advertising Initiative website here - http://optout.networkadvertising.org/?c=1 or the EDAA opt-out program here – http://www.youronlinechoice.eu or in respect of mobile devices http://www.aboutads.info/appchoices - please note that we're not responsible for the content of external websites. You can block cookies by activating the setting on your browser that allows you to refuse the setting of all or some cookies. However, if you use your browser settings to block all cookies (including essential cookies) you may not be able to access all or parts of the site. If you download an app to receive the services in respect of this site, we will also (where you agree that we may do so) collect geo-location data in relation to the device that you are using. While your browser may also allow you to send a “do not track” signal when you visit our site, we do not modify our practices in response to the signal. We will continue to comply with this Privacy Policy in any event. Back to top
DIFFERENCES BETWEEN VERSIONS If there is an inconsistency between the English version of this Privacy Policy and the Swedish version of this Privacy Policy, the English version will take priority (unless your personal information was collected from you in Sweden, in which case the Swedish version will take priority). Back to top
LES MILLS NORDISKA INTEGRITETSPOLICY
introduktion Les Mills värnar skyddet för och respekten av din integritet. Det är med stöd av denna policy (tillsammans med våra webbplatsvillkor, inköpsvillkor och eventuella andra villkor som anges på vår hemsida från tid till annan och meddelas på annan del av hemsidan) som vi kommer att behandla de personuppgifter vi samlar in från dig eller som du lämnar till oss. Vänligen läs följande noggrant för att förstå vår praxis gällande behandlingen av dina personuppgifter och hur vi kommer att behandla dessa. Den här policyn kan förändras från tid till annan. Om den gör det kommer den senaste versionen att finnas tillgänglig på vår hemsida och i vår app. När det bedöms lämpligt kommer du att uppmärksammas på en sådan förändring. Denna integritetspolicy uppdaterades senast den 4 May 2018. Viktigt:
Les Mills Nordic AB är personuppgiftsansvarig för personuppgifter som behandlas genom användning av vår hemsida eller app. De personuppgifter som vi behandlar inkluderar information som du lämnar när du använder vår hemsida eller våra tjänster, teknisk information om din enhet, inställningar och webbplatsanvändning, information som vi tar emot från tredje part, såsom andra webbplatsleverantörer, annonsnätverk, sociala medier och hälso- och fitnessklubbar, och om det är aktuellt, information om din roll som instruktör. Vi använder bl.a. dina uppgifter för att tillhandahålla dig vår webbplats och våra tjänster eller information om vår webbplats och våra tjänster, skräddarsy våra tjänster för dig, utföra analys av våra tjänster, tillhandahålla (eller tillåta andra att tillhandahålla) riktade annonser, följa lagstadgade eller regulatoriska skyldigheter och (om du är instruktör) utvärdera din prestation och ge information som relaterar till din roll som instruktör. Vi kan skicka marknadsföringsmaterial till dig som avser våra tjänster. Du kan välja bort det när som helst. Vi delar uppgifter med våra tjänsteleverantörer och andra tredje parter för utförandet av våra avtalsförpliktelser gentemot dig, för att förse dig med information, för visning av reklam och (i förekommande fall) köra kredit- och bakgrundskontroller. Du har ett antal rättigheter som du kan utöva i samband med vår användning av dina personuppgifter. Du kan utöva dessa rättigheter genom att kontakta oss via de kommunikationsmetoder som anges i avsnittet "Dina rättigheter" nedan.
Du kan hitta information om oss och hur vi samlar in, använder och lagrar dina personuppgifter i vart och ett av avsnitten i denna policy:
Vilka är vi
Information vi samlar in från dig Hur din information kommer att användas
Utlämnande av dina uppgifter
Les Mills instruktörer
Där vi lagrar sina personuppgifter och internationella överföringar Datalagring Informationssäkerhet Sociala nätverk Länkade hemsidor Allmänna forum Barn
Dina rättigheter
Ändringar i vår integritetspolicy Kontakt Cookies Motstridiga villkorsversioner
VILKA ÄR VI Denna webbplats och vår app (”sidorna”) drivs av Les Mills Nordic AB, Oxenstiernsgatan 15A, 115 27 Stockholm, Sverige (”vi", "oss", "vår"). Medan våra instruktörs- och klubbportaler slutligen styrs av oss utförs den dagliga driften av dessa portaler av följande Les Mills-företag inom ditt territorium. Les Mills UK Fitness Limited driver brittiska instruktörs och klubbportaler, Les Mills United States Trading Inc., driver amerikansk instruktör och klubbportaler och Les Mills Nordic AB driver de nordiska instruktörs och klubbportalerna. Vi, tillsammans med det relevanta Les Mills Company på ditt territorium (om du använder vår instruktör eller klubbportaler), är controllers, dvs ansvarig för behandlingen av din personliga information. I denna integritetspolicy avses med "Les Mills-företag" Les Mills International Limited samt alla dotterbolag och närstående företag som från tid till annan ägs av Les Mills International Limited (förutom oss). Om du vill ha en fullständig lista över alla etablissemang som omfattas av Les Mills-företag, vänligen kontakta oss på sätt som beskrivs under "Kontakt" nedan. Med ”Instruktör” avses en person som har rätt att instruera Les Mills program eller som har träffat ett instruktörsavtal med oss (”Instruktörsavtal”). tillbaka till toppen
INFORMATION VI SAMLAR IN FRÅN DIG Vi kommer att samla in och behandla följande uppgifter om dig: Information du ger oss Det rör sig om uppgifter om dig som du ger oss när du surfar eller använder sidorna, kontaktar oss via telefon, SMS, e-post, sociala medier eller på annat sätt. Informationen innehåller uppgifter som du lämnar till oss när:
du registrera dig för att använda våra sidor, prenumerera på vår tjänst, söker efter en produkt, beställer en produkt på våra sidor, medverkar i diskussioner eller andra funktioner via sociala medier på våra sidor, deltar i en tävling, du anmäler ett problem på våra sidor.
Den information du ger oss innefattar ditt namn, din adress, ditt födelsedatum, din e-postadress och ditt telefonnummer, din finansiella- och kreditkortsinformation, din personliga beskrivning och dina fotografier, videor, bilder och kommentarer. Om du är en Instruktör kommer vi att samla in ytterligare information om dig hänförlig till din roll som Instruktör, inbegripet information om de klasser du undervisar i och de klubbar du är ansluten till, inköpshistoria, betalningsinformation, närvaro under evenemang/utbildning, certifieringsinformation och arbetade timmar. Information vi samlar in om dig. När det gäller vart och ett av dina besök på våra sidor kommer vi automatiskt att samla in följande information:
teknisk information, inklusive den IP-adress som används för att ansluta datorn eller enheten till Internet, dina inloggningsuppgifter, typ av webbläsare och version, inställning för tidszon, anonymiserad platsdata, plug-in-typer och versioner på din webbläsare, operativsystem och plattform; information om ditt besök, inklusive den fullständiga webbadressen, klick till, genom och från vår webbplats (inklusive datum och tid), sidor eller produkter som du tittade på eller sökte efter, svarstider, hämtningsfel, besökslängd på vissa sidor, information om interaktion på sidor (såsom scrollning, klick, och mouseovers), metoder som används för att bläddra bort från sidan.
Information vi får från andra källor. Andra Les Mills-sidor: Vi kommer att ta emot information om dig om du använder någon av de andra webbplatser som drivs av Les Mills-företag eller andra tjänster som Les Millsföretag tillhandahåller. Tredje part: Vi samarbetar också nära med tredje part (inklusive, till exempel, affärspartners, auktoriserade återförsäljare, hälso- och/eller fitnessklubbar eller andra företag som har rätt att tillhandahålla Les Mills program (”Licensierade Klubbar”), underleverantörer inom tekniska, betalnings- och leveranstjänster, annonsnätverk, analysleverantörer, annonsörer, leverantörer av sökmotorer, kreditupplysningsföretag, tredje parter som gör det möjligt för s.k ”sign on-funktionalitet” och integration via sociala nätverk) och kommer att ta emot information om dig från dem. Social Media: Om du ansluter dig till oss via vissa sociala medier, eller om du väljer att använda funktioner på denna hemsida eller andra Les Mills-företags hemsidor som ansluter till dina online-profiler eller konton på sociala medier ("Social Media Konton"), kommer vi att samla alla uppgifter som du tillåter genom inställningarna på dessa Social Media Konton. Till exempel, om du loggar in på vår hemsida med ditt Facebook-konto och du har tillåtit Facebook att dela profilinformation med oss, kommer vi att samla in sådana uppgifter. Uppgifter vi får från dina Social Media Konton kan inkludera e-postadress, för- och efternamn, plats (hemstad och land), kön, födelsedatum, likes, intressen, antalet anslutningar, yrke, inlägg eller annan social verksamhet. Den information som din sociala medieplattform kan förse oss med via ditt Social Media Konton kan ändras från tid till annan. Vänligen granska dina Social Media Konton och dess sekretessinställningar för att kontrollera vilken information som delas med oss. tillbaka till toppen
HHUR DIN INFORMATION KOMMER ATT ANVÄNDAS Vi använder informationen om dig på följande sätt. När det är möjligt så anonymiserar vi data så att den inte kan kopplas till någon enskild person. Information du ger oss (bland annat genom Social Media Konton) A. Vi kommer att behandla uppgifter för följande syften med stöd av våra berättiga intressen:
förse dig med information om andra varor och tjänster som vi erbjuder och som liknar de som du redan har köpt eller frågat om; för att säkerställa att innehåll från vår webbplats presenteras på det mest effektiva sättet för dig och för din dator; för att skräddarsy din upplevelse på webbplatsen; för dataanalys, testande, forskning, statistik, redaktionella ändamål, för att få feedback och i undersökningsändamål; • för att följa lagar och bestämmelser.
B. Vi kommer att behandla uppgifter för följande syften för att vi ska kunna fullgöra ett avtal:
utföra våra skyldigheter som följer av eventuella avtal som ingåtts mellan dig och oss; svara på dina frågor; förse dig med information, produkter och tjänster som du efterfrågar av oss; informera dig om ändringar i vår tjänst; möjliggöra för dig att dela information på vår webbplats och på tredje parts sociala medier.
C. Vi kommer att behandla uppgifter för följande syften med stöd av ditt samtycke:
för att förse dig med den senaste informationen och de senaste erbjudandena avseende hälsa och fitness eller för att ge behöriga tredje parter möjlighet att ge dig information om varor och tjänster; för att anmäla dig till Reebok One för att kunna få 25% rabatt om du är en Les Mills-instruktör.
Information vi samlar in om dig. A. Vi kommer att behandla uppgifter för följande syften med stöd av våra berättiga intressen:
för att administrera vår webbplats och för interna verksamheter, inklusive felsökningar, dataanalyser, testning, forsknings-, statistiska och undersökningsändamål; för att förbättra våra sidor för att se till att innehållet presenteras på det mest effektiva sättet för dig och för din dator; som en del av våra ansträngningar för att hålla sidorna trygga och säkra; för att mäta eller förstå effektiviteten av den reklam vi erbjuder dig och andra, och för att leverera relevanta annonser till dig; för att lämna förslag och rekommendationer till dig och andra användare rörande våra sidor om varor eller tjänster som kan vara av intresse för dig eller dem; för att tillhandahålla (eller tillåta tredje part att tillhandahålla) riktad reklam via sidor du besöker om varor eller tjänster som kan vara av intresse för dig (se mer om detta i vår Cookie-sektion nedan); för att följa utvecklingen och antalet inlägg i tävlingar och kampanjer.
B. Vi kommer att behandla uppgifter för följande syften med stöd av ditt samtycke:
för att du ska kunna ta del av interaktiva funktioner i vår tjänst, när du väljer att göra det;
Information vi får från andra källor. Vi kommer att kombinera information som vi får från andra källor med information som du ger till oss och information som vi samlar in om dig. Vi kommer att använda denna information och den kombinerade informationen i de syften som anges ovan (beroende på vilken typ av information vi får). tillbaka till toppen
UTLÄMNANDE AV DINA UPPGIFTER Tjänsteleverantörer För några av de ändamål för vilka vi använder personuppgifter (se ovan), kommer vi att engagera en tredje part. Om en sådan tredje part är i behov av tillgång till personuppgifter för att kunna fullgöra sin uppgift, kommer vi att dela data med denne, vi kommer att se till att denne tredje part endast kommer att använda denna data utifrån våra instruktioner. En sådan tredje part är ett personuppgiftsbiträde för vår räkning och vi kommer att fortsätta att ansvara för din data. Vi kommer att engagera följande personuppgiftsbiträden:
Företag som tillhandahåller tjänster till oss (inklusive Les Mills-företag), såsom leverantörer, tjänsteleverantörer och andra partners som stöder vår verksamhet globalt. Dessa tredje parter tillhandahåller tjänster såsom tekniska infrastrukturtjänster som analyserar hur våra tjänster används och mäter effektiviteten hos annonser och andra tjänster, tillhandahåller kundservice, ombesörjer betalningar eller genomför akademiska studier. Med dessa parter ingår vi sekretessåtaganden och de måste uppfylla sekretessåtaganden som är i linje med denna policy; och • Analytics och sökmotorleverantörer som hjälper oss att förbättra och optimera vår webbplats. Vi vill att vår webbplats och annonsering ska vara så relevant och intressant för dig som den kan vara. Med det i åtanke använder vi all information som vi har om dig för att visa relevanta annonser och för att kunna optimera våra sidor. Vi delar inte med oss av information som identifierar dig (det gäller information som namn eller e-postadress som i sig kan användas för att kontakta dig eller identifiera vem du är) genom annonsering, mätning eller analys, om du inte ger oss tillåtelse. Vi kan ge dessa parter information om deras annonserings räckvidd och effektivitet utan att ge dem information som personligen identifierar dig, eller om vi har sammanställt informationen så att den inte identifierar dig personligen.
Andra tredje parter Vi kommer, baserat på ditt uttryckliga medgivande, eller på annat sätt när vi har rätt att göra detta i enlighet med aktuella personuppgiftsregelverk, att dela dina personuppgifter med:
Les Mills-företag; följande utvalda tredje parter
affärspartners, auktoriserade distributörer, leverantörer, tjänsteleverantörer, Les Mills licensierade klubbar och underleverantörer för att utföra de avtal vi går in i med dig; affärspartners, auktoriserade distributörer, leverantörer, tjänsteleverantörer, Les Mills licensierade klubbar och underleverantörer för att ge dig information om kampanjer och erbjudanden, eller för några av de andra ändamål som beskrivs i sektionen "Hur informationen kommer att användas" ovan. annonsörer och annonsnätverk som behöver data för att välja och servera relevant reklam för dig och andra. Utöver det som anges i punkten direkt nedan, kommer vi inte lämna ut information om identifierbara individer till våra annonsörer, men vi kommer att ge dem sammanställd information om våra användare (t ex kan vi informera dem om att 500 män under 30 år har klickat på deras annons under en viss dag). Vi kommer också att använda sådan samlad information för att hjälpa annonsörer att nå den typ av publik de vill rikta sig till (t ex kvinnor med en viss postnummer). Vi kommer att använda de personuppgifter vi har samlat in från dig för att göra det möjligt för oss att uppfylla våra annonsörers önskemål genom att visa sin reklam som når deras önskade målgrupp, sociala medier eller andra liknande plattformar så att vi kan bistå med relevant innehåll till dig via den plattformen. Till exempel kan vi dela din e-postadress med Facebook så att vi kan inkludera dig i en anpassad målgrupp som vi (eller en tredje part för vår räkning) kommer att bistå information med till Facebook, eller så kan vi skapa en publik med andra Facebook-användare baserat på informationen i din Facebook-profil. kreditupplysningsföretag för att bedöma ditt kreditvärde när detta är en förutsättning för oss att ingå i ett avtal med dig.
Utlämnande av information under visa omständigheter Vi kommer, baserat på ditt uttryckliga medgivande eller på annat sätt när vi har rätt att göra det i enlighet med gällande personuppgiftslagstiftning också lämna ut din personliga information till tredje part, i följande fall:
Om vi säljer eller köper företag eller tillgångar kommer vi att lämna ut dina personuppgifter till potentiella säljare eller köpare av sådant företag eller tillgångar. Om Les Mills-företag som kontrollerar denna webbplats eller huvudsakligen alla dess tillgångar förvärvas av tredje part, och de personuppgifter som innehas om kunderna är en av de överförda tillgångarna. Om vi är skyldiga att lämna ut eller dela dina personuppgifter i syfte att uppfylla någon juridisk förpliktelse, eller i syfte att upprätthålla eller tillämpa våra webbplatsvillkor, inköpsvillkor, och andra avtal, eller för att skydda rättigheter, egendom eller säkerhet av något Les Mills-företag, våra kunder eller andra. Detta omfattar utbyte av information med andra företag och organisationer i syfte att skydda mot bedrägerier och minska kreditrisken. Där du har annars har lämnat ditt samtycke till att vi får göra det.
tillbaka till toppen
LES MILLS INSTRUKTÖRER Ytterligare ändamål för vilka Instruktörernas personuppgifter kommer att användas
Vi (eller Licensierade Klubbar) kan ge Instruktörer möjlighet att dela med sig av sin personliga information med Licensierade Klubbar via vår klubbportal https://sso.lesmills.com/login (”Club Portal”). Om Instruktörerna samtycker till att dela med sig av sin personliga information via Club Portal, kommer Licensierade Klubbar kunna få tillgång till, bearbeta och använda personlig information för att: (i) underlätta och upprätthålla relationen mellan den Licensierade Klubben och instruktören; (ii) köpa Instruktör program kits (“Instruktör Releases”) på uppdrag av utsedda Instruktörer; (iii) köpa evenemangsbiljetter på uppdrag av utsedda Instruktörer; (iv) Kontakta, eller svara på, kontaktförfrågningar från Instruktörer som söker Licensierade Klubbar att ansluta sig till; och (v) för andra ändamål som krävs enligt lag eller lagligen är tillåtet från tid till annan. Om du är en Licensierad Klubb och du förser oss med personlig information om Instruktörerna (”Instruktörsinformation”), garanterar du härmed att du har alla nödvändiga samtycken enligt tillämplig lag att delge oss Instruktörsinformation samt att vi kan använda Instruktörsinformationen i enlighet med denna integritetspolicy. Du samtycket till att försvara och hålla oss skadelösa från och mot alla anspråk, kostnader, förluster, skulder och skador som uppstår på grund av vår användning av Instruktörsinformationen i enlighet med denna integritetspolicy. Om du är en Instruktör, kommer vi också att använda informationen som du ger oss, som vi samlar in om dig eller som vi får från andra källor, för följande ändamål (för att fullgöra ett avtal med dig eller, när det inte är aktuellt, med stöd av våra berättigade intressen):
Översyn, hantering och administration av alla aspekter av din roll som Instruktör (inklusive hur du fullgör dina instruktörsuppgifter, utvärdering därav och din betalningshistorik) (inbegripet att ge dig tillgång till Less Mills instructörsportal på http://w2.lesmills.com/home/login (”Instruktör Portal”) samt information om utbildning, utvärdering, certifiering och utbudet av Instruktör Releases); Tillhandahålla din(a) Licensierade Klubb(ar) information hänförlig till dig avseende certifiering, fortbildning, utvärdering och utbildning; Se till att de Licensierade Klubbarna du är ansluten till uppfyller sina förpliktelser gentemot oss; Se till att du uppfyller villkoren i ditt Instruktörsavtal och villkoren på Instruktör Portal samt fullgör eventuella rättsliga skyldigheter i anslutning därtill; Ledning och övervakning av gruppträningar (inklusive Instruktörens agerande) vid Licensierade Klubbar och analys av trender och tendenser inom fitness-industrin.
Ytterligare användning av instruktörens personuppgifter
Vi kommer att, baserat på ditt uttryckliga medgivande eller på annat sätt när vi har rätt att göra det i enlighet med gällande personuppgiftslagstiftning, publicera ditt namn i nyhetsbrev och på våra webbplatser när det gäller din roll som instruktör.
tillbaka till toppen
DÄR VI LAGRAR DINA PERSONUPPGIFTER OCH INTERNATIONELLA ÖVERFÖRINGAR Individer (särskilt inom Europeiska ekonomiska samarbetsområdet, eller "EES") bör vara medvetna om att vi och andra tredjepartsmottagare av deras personuppgifter, såsom Les Mills-företag eller våra tjänsteleverantörer inte kommer att vara belägna inom din jurisdiktion eller inom EES. Personuppgifter kan, till exempel, komma att föras över till Nya Zeeland i anslutning till de syften som angetts ovan. Åtgärder kommer att vidtas för att skydda dina personuppgifter i överensstämmelse med gällande lag, till exempel genom att ingå avtal vars bestämmelser speglar de av EU framtagna standardavtalsklausulerna när personuppgifter avseende medborgare inom EU delas med en part utanför EES som är baserad i ett land som inte anses ha tillräckligt skydd för personuppgifter. All information du lämnar till oss lagras på våra säkra servrar eller på säkra servrar eller säkra tjänster som kontrolleras av tredje part för vår räkning. Eventuella betaltransaktioner kommer att krypteras med hjälp av SSL-teknik. Där vi har gett dig (eller där du har valt) ett lösenord som ger dig tillgång till vissa delar av vår webbplats så är du ansvarig för att hålla detta lösenord hemligt. Vi ber dig att inte dela lösenordet med någon. Tyvärr är överföring av information via Internet inte helt säkert. Även om vi gör vårt bästa för att skydda dina personuppgifter så kan vi inte garantera säkerheten för din data som överförs till vår webbplats; överföring sker på egen risk. När vi har fått dina uppgifter kommer vi att använda strikta rutiner och säkerhetsfunktioner för att försöka förhindra obehörig åtkomst. tillbaka till toppen
DATALAGRING Vi lagrar bara personuppgifter som vi samlat in om det behövs av motiverade affärsmässiga överväganden eller när våra lagliga syften för användning av uppgifterna kräver lagring. När vi inte längre behöver personuppgifterna kommer vi eller våra leverantörer att på ett säkert sätt radera och/eller arkivera informationen. Kontakta oss på info.nordic@lesmills.com för mer information om var och hur länge sina personuppgifter lagras och för mer information om dina rättigheter när det gäller radering och portabilitet. tillbaka till toppen
INFORMATIONSSÄKERHET För att skydda personuppgifterna och personligt identifierbar information som du överför genom användningen av våra sidor så har vi vidtagit fysiska, tekniska och administrativa skyddsåtgärder. Vi uppdaterar och testar kontinuerligt vår säkerhetsteknik. Vi begränsar tillgången till dina personuppgifter till de anställda som behöver ha informationen för att kunna tillhandahålla erbjudanden om förmåner eller tjänster till dig. Dessutom utbildar vi våra anställda i vikten av sekretess och att upprätthålla integritet och säkerhet. Vi förbinder oss att vidta lämpliga disciplinära åtgärder för att upprätthålla våra anställdas integritetsansvar. tillbaka till toppen
SOCIALA NÄTVERK Du kan logga in på vår hemsida med hjälp av inloggningstjänster såsom Facebook Connect. Dessa tjänster kommer att verifiera din identitet och ger dig möjlighet att dela vissa personuppgifter med oss såsom namn och e-postadress för att i förväg fylla inloggningsformuläret. Tjänster som Facebook Connect ger dig möjlighet att publicera information om dina aktiviteter på denna webbplats på din profilsida för att dela det med andra inom nätverket. tillbaka till toppen
LÄNKADE HEMSIDOR Denna hemsida, våra nyhetsbrev och annan kommunikation kommer från tid till annan att innehålla länkar och/eller banners som tar dig till andra webbplatser. Vi är inte ansvariga för tillförlitligheten av innehållet eller integritetspraxis på sådana andra hemsidor. Vår hemsida kan även innehålla sociala media-funktioner, till exempel Facebooks like-knapp. Dessa funktioner kommer att samla in din IP-adress, vilken sida du besöker på vår hemsida, och kommer att lämna en cookie för att möjligöra det för funktionen att fungera korrekt. Värden för sociala media-funktionerna är antingen en tredje part eller vår webbplats. Din interaktion med dessa funktioner skyddas även av den integritetspolicy som tillhör det företag som tillhandahåller den. tillbaka till toppen
ALLMÄNNA FORUM Vi kan förse dig med chattfunktioner, snabbmeddelanden, anslagstavlor, diskussionsforum och/eller nyhetsgrupper genom webbplatsen eller på annat sätt. Kom ihåg att all information som du lämnar i allmänna utrymmen på webbplatsen blir offentlig information och kommer att vara tillgänglig för allmänheten. Vi avser inte (men förbehåller oss rätten) att övervaka, moderera och screena innehållet i användarnas inlägg. Vi bär inget ansvar för sådant innehåll och du bör vara försiktig när du överväger att lämna ut dina personuppgifter på hemsidan via offentliga eller privata forum. tillbaka till toppen
BARN Vi samlar inte medvetet in information från barn under 16 års ålder och varken hemsidan eller andra tillhörande appar är riktade till barn under 16 år. Vi uppmuntrar föräldrar och vårdnadshavare att bevara en aktiv roll i sina barns intressen och aktiviteter online. tillbaka till toppen
DINA RÄTTIGHETER Tillgång till dina personuppgifter
Du har rätt att begära att få tillgång till vissa personuppgifter som vi har om dig, inklusive all information som vi har delat med Les Mills-företag eller en tredje part och/eller våra personuppgiftsbiträden, under vissa villkor och med vissa begränsade undantag som anges i relevanta personuppgiftslagar. Om så önskas, maila din förfrågan till info@lesmills.com. Vi kommer att vara så öppna som vi kan med dig men ibland har vi kanske inte några personuppgifter om dig eller så måste vi kanske hemlighålla information från dig. Till exempel om informationen inte utgör dina personuppgifter, är kommersiellt känslig, är juridiskt privilegierad, avser någon annans personuppgifter, eller om det kan påverka våra anställdas eller kunders säkerhet om vi skulle släppa informationen. Under dessa omständigheter kommer vi att hemlighålla informationen. Vi kommer i så fall att förklara varför. Du måste förse oss med korrekt information. Om någon av dina uppgifter ändras, vänligen meddela oss så uppdaterar vi dina personuppgifter i enlighet med våra skyldigheter i aktuella regelverk. Du har rätt att be oss att inte använda dina personuppgifter i marknadsföringssyfte. Vi brukar informera dig (innan vi samlar in din data) om vi har för avsikt att använda dina uppgifter för sådana ändamål eller om vi har för avsikt att lämna ut din information till tredje part för dessa ändamål. Du kan utöva rätten genom att när som helst genom att kontakta oss påinfo@lesmills.com eller genom att använda någon annan opt-out-metod som vi tillhandahåller i vår kommunikation, såsom till exempel att använda länken för avregistrering i e-mail. Du kan, utöver de rättigheter som anges ovan, ha särskilda rättigheter enligt dataskyddslagstiftningen i Europeiska unionen. Om denna lagstiftning ska tillämpas på dig kan du också begära information om: syftet med behandlingen; de kategorier av personuppgifter som berörs; vem som, utanför Les Mills-företagen, kan ha fått uppgifterna från oss; vem källan till informationen var (om inte du gav dem direkt till oss); och hur länge de kommer att lagras. Du har rätt att:
begära att vi korrigerar registreringen av dina personuppgifter som upprätthållas av oss om registreringen är felaktig eller föråldrad; begära att vi raderar denna data eller slutar behandla den, med vissa undantag; be oss att inte behandla dina personuppgifter för de legitima intressen som vi har angivit ovan. Det är inte säkert att vi kan sluta använda dina personuppgifter men i så fall kommer vi att meddela dig och berätta varför; ta emot den personliga information som du har lämnat till oss i ett strukturerat, vanligt och maskinläsbart format och att överföra denna data till en annan personuppgiftsansvarig och att lämna in ett klagomål till lämplig dataskyddsmyndighet om du känner oro över hur vi behandlar dina personuppgifter.
Var vänlig och skicka din begäran till info@lesmills.comom du vill utöva någon av ovanstående rättigheter. tillbaka till toppen
ÄNDRINGAR I VÅR INTEGRITETSPOLICY Alla förändringar vi gör i vår integritetspolicy i framtiden kommer att publiceras på denna sida och meddelas dig via e-post. Vänligen återvänd ofta för att ta del av eventuella uppdateringar eller förändringar i vår integritetspolicy. tillbaka till toppen
KONTAKT Frågor, kommentarer och förfrågningar angående denna integritetspolicy är välkomna och bör ställas till info@lesmills.com. Vår adress är Oxenstiernsgatan 15A, 115 27 Stockholm, Sverige. tillbaka till toppen
COOKIES Webbplatsen använder cookies för att skilja dig från andra användare. Detta hjälper oss att ge dig en bra upplevelse när du surfar på sidan och tillåter oss också att förbättra hemsidan. En cookie är en liten fil med bokstäver och siffror som vi lagrar i din webbläsare eller på hårddisken i datorn. Cookies innehåller information som överförs till datorns hårddisk. Vi använder följande cookies:
Strikt nödvändiga cookies. Dessa är cookies som krävs för driften av webbplatsen. De omfattar till exempel cookies som gör att du kan logga in på säkra delar av webbplatsen. Analytiska-/prestandacookies. De tillåter oss att känna igen och räkna antalet besökare och se hur besökarna rör sig på webbplatsen när de använder den. Detta hjälper oss att förbättra det sätt på vilket hemsidan fungerar, till exempel genom att se till att användarna enkelt kan hitta vad de letar efter. Cookies för ökad funktionalitet. Dessa används för att känna igen dig när du återvänder till webbplatsen. Detta gör det möjligt för oss att anpassa vårt innehåll för dig, välkomna genom användning av ditt namn och komma ihåg dina preferenser (till exempel språkval eller region). Inriktade cookies. Dessa cookies registrerar ditt besök på webbplatsen, vilka sidor du har besökt och de länkar som du har följt. Vi kommer att använda denna information för att göra webbplatsen och den reklam som visas på den mer relevant för dina intressen. Vi delar också denna information med tredje part för detta ändamål.
Vissa sidor på webbplatsen och våra e-postmeddelanden innehåller små elektroniska filer som kallas webbsignaler (även kallad ”clear gifs”, pixeltaggar och ”single-pixel gifs”) som normalt arbetar i samband med cookies för att identifiera våra användare och användarbeteende över tid, till exempel för att räkna antalet användare som har besökt vissa hemsidor eller öppnat e-post och för annan relaterad webbplatsstatistik (till exempel registrering av populariteten av visst webbplatsinnehåll och kontrollera system- och serverintegritet). Observera att tredje part (inklusive till exempel annonsnätverk och leverantörer av externa tjänster som webbtrafik) även använder cookies på vår hemsida som vi inte har någon kontroll över. Dessa cookies kommer sannolikt att vara analytiska-/prestandacookies eller inriktade cookies. Annonsnätverk i synnerhet samlar in information om dina online-aktiviteter över tid och mellan olika webbplatser och använder denna information för att tillhandahålla intressebaserad reklam eller annat riktat innehåll. Om du vill välja bort intressebaserad annonsering, gå till Network Advertising Initiative’s hemsida här - https://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/ eller EDAA opt-out programmet här – http://www.youronlinechoices.eu observera att vi inte är ansvariga för innehållet på externa webbplatser. Du kan blockera cookies genom att aktivera inställningen på din webbläsare som gör att du kan vägra ta emot alla eller vissa cookies. Men om du använder webbläsarens inställningar för att blockera alla cookies (inklusive viktiga cookies) kan det hända att du inte kommer åt alla delar av hemsidan. Om du laddar ner en app för att ta emot tjänster för denna sida kommer vi också (där du samtycker till att vi får göra det) samla geo-lokaliseringsuppgifter i förhållande till den enhet som du använder. Även om webbläsaren också kan tillåta dig att skicka en "spåra inte"-signal när du besöker vår hemsida så ändrar vi inte våra rutiner till följd av signalen. Under alla omständigheter kommer vi att fortsätta följa denna integritetspolicy. tillbaka till toppen
MOTSTRIDIGA VILLKORSVERSIONER Vid motstridigheter mellan den engelska versionen av denna integritetspolicy och den svenska versionen, ska den engelska versionen ha företräde (såvida inte din personliga information samlades in från dig i Sverige, i vilket fall den svenska versionen ska ha företräde). tillbaka till toppen
